A Guide to the Russell Sage Foundation records FA015
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Russell Sage Foundation records, 1885-1983; 1907-1948; 1; 64.5 Cubic Feet 145 document cases
  - Personal Giving, 1879-1919, bulk 1906-1918; 1906-1918; 10; 18 Cubic Feet 41 boxes
    - Institutions, 1879-1919, undated; 1
      - Woman's Civic Improvement League (Kalamazoo, Michigan), 1907 (Box 96, Folder 977)
      - Woman's Hospital, 1879-1918 (Box 97, Folder 978)
      - Woman's Hospital, 1879-1918 (Box 97, Folder 979)
      - Woman's Hospital, 1879-1918 (Box 97, Folder 980)
      - Woman's Hospital, 1879-1918 (Box 97, Folder 981)
      - Woman's Hospital - Addresses by Mrs. Sage, 1892-1894, 1901, undated (Box 97, Folder 982)
      - Woman's Hospital - Ledger Book, 1883, 1899 (Box 97, Folder 983)
      - Woman's Hotel Company, 1903-1912 (Box 98, Folder 984)
      - Woman's International Review, 1912-1913 (Box 98, Folder 985)
      - Woman's Legal Education Society, 1903 (Box 98, Folder 986)
      - Woman's Municipal League, 1908-1918 (Box 98, Folder 987)
      - Woman's National Sabbath Alliance, 1906-1917 (Box 98, Folder 988)
      - Woman's National War Relief, 1898 (Box 98, Folder 989)
      - Woman's Union Missionary Society, 1911, 1914 (Box 98, Folder 990)
      - Women and Children's Hospital (and) Hospital of Good Shepherd (Syracuse, New York), 1907, 1909, 1915 (Box 98, Folder 991)
      - Women's Guild of St. John Chapel (Flushing, NY), 1909, undated (Box 98, Folder 992)
      - Women's Health Protective Association, 1909 (Box 98, Folder 993)
      - Women's League for National Service, Undated (Box 98, Folder 994)
      - Women's Suffrage, 1909-1918, undated (Box 98, Folder 995)
      - Women's Suffrage, 1909-1918, undated (Box 98, Folder 996)
      - Women's Suffrage, 1902-1918, undated (Box 99, Folder 997)
      - Working Girls Vacation Society, 1913-1914 (Box 99, Folder 998)
      - Working Women's Protective Union, 1902-1917 (Box 99, Folder 999)
      - World Missionary Conference, 1909 (Box 99, Folder 1000)
      - Yale University, 1907-1911, 1917, undated (Box 99, Folder 1001)
      - Young Helpers' League, 1905, 1915-1916 (Box 99, Folder 1002)
      - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - Army Branch, 1907-1917 (Box 99, Folder 1003)
      - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - Army-Navy Books and Calendars, undated (Box 99, Folder 1004)
      - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - Army-Navy Books and Calendars, undated (Box 100, Folder 1005)
      - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - Army-Navy Books and Calendars, undated (Box 100, Folder 1006)
      - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - General, 1886-1917 (Box 100, Folder 1007)
      - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - General, 1886-1917 (Box 100, Folder 1008)
      - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - International Committee (Army-Navy Department), 1906-1917 (Box 100, Folder 1009)
      - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - International Committee Women's Auxiliary, 1901-1917, undated (Box 101, Folder 1010)
      - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - Navy Branch, 1903-1917 (Box 101, Folder 1011)
      - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA)-Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) Joint Campaign, 1913, 1917 (Box 101, Folder 1012)
      - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - General, 1904-1918, undated (Box 101, Folder 1013)
      - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - General, 1904-1918, undated (Box 101, Folder 1014)
      - Zenana Bible and Medical Mission, 1903 (Box 101, Folder 1015)
    - Individual Legatees, 1885-1919, undated; 2
      Subseries 2 contains correspondence from individual legatees. A summary of the giving to individual legatees (found in Box 106, folder 1059) may be helpful when used in conjunction with those files.
      - Baisley, Mary, 1905-1919 (Box 102, Folder 1016)
      - Barrett, Harriet Strong, 1906 (Box 102, Folder 1017)
      - Barrow, Mary, 1906-1918 (Box 102, Folder 1018)
      - Buckingham, Eva, 1908-1911, 1919, undated (Box 102, Folder 1019)
      - Burnet, Ethel, 1915 (Box 102, Folder 1020)
      - Cheeseman, Miriam, 1903-1914, 1919 (Box 102, Folder 1021)
      - Cole, Lucetta, 1902-1919 (Box 102, Folder 1022)
      - Cole, Lucetta, 1902-1919 (Box 102, Folder 1023)
      - Cole, Lucetta, 1902-1919 (Box 103, Folder 1024)
      - Fischer, Louise, 1903-1919 (Box 103, Folder 1025)
      - Fischer, Louise, 1903-1919 (Box 103, Folder 1026)
      - Fitch, Louise, 1900-1919 (Box 103, Folder 1027)
      - Fitch, Louise, 1900-1919 (Box 103, Folder 1028)
      - Fitch, Louise, 1900-1919 (Box 104, Folder 1029)
      - Hubbard, Henrietta, 1900-1917, undated (Box 104, Folder 1030)
      - Indian Industrial School, 1885-1913 (Box 104, Folder 1031)
      - Kilbourne, Alanson Jermain and Kilbourne Family, 1904-1919 (Box 104, Folder 1032)
      - Lansing, Emily, 1919 (Box 104, Folder 1033)
      - Lawrence, Elizabeth Spooner, 1906-1919 (Box 104, Folder 1034)
      - Lawrence, Margaret S., 1904-1917 (Box 104, Folder 1035)
      - Lawton, Annie, 1908-1909, 1914 (Box 104, Folder 1036)
      - Lawton, Eba Anderson, 1911 (Box 104, Folder 1037)
      - Lawton, Henrietta Beebe, 1894-1918 (Box 104, Folder 1038)
      - Lawton, Henrietta Beebe, 1894-1918 (Box 104, Folder 1039)
      - Mallouf, Hannah, 1887-1888, 1903-1912 (Box 104, Folder 1040)
      - McCammon, Kate, 1905-1918 (Box 105, Folder 1041)
      - Norton, John H., 1906 (Box 105, Folder 1042)
      - Pierson, Harriet and Pierson, Mary, 1906-1919 (Box 105, Folder 1043)
      - Pierson, Samuel C., 1907-1919 (Box 105, Folder 1044)
      - Porter, Nellie, 1907 (Box 105, Folder 1045)
      - Prime-Stevenson, E. I., 1912-1919 (Box 105, Folder 1046)
      - Reddish, Julia, 1909, 1919 (Box 105, Folder 1047)
      - Sage, Mrs. Elisha, 1919 (Box 105, Folder 1048)
      - Southard, Caroline, 1907-1912 (Box 105, Folder 1049)
      - Spooner, Emma M., 1903, 1919, undated (Box 105, Folder 1050)
      - Spooner, Sarah, 1907, 1911, 1919 (Box 105, Folder 1051)
      - Stevenson, Preston, 1908-1919 (Box 106, Folder 1052)
      - Stille, Mary, 1901-1919 (Box 106, Folder 1053)
      - Stille, Mary, 1901-1919 (Box 106, Folder 1054)
      - Strong, Alma Barton, 1899 (Box 106, Folder 1055)
      - Strong, Edith, 1919 (Box 106, Folder 1056)
      - Strong, Elizabeth, 1911 (Box 106, Folder 1057)
      - Strong, Mary, 1908-1918, undated (Box 106, Folder 1058)
      - Summary File of Legatees and Pensioners, undated (Box 106, Folder 1059)
      - Thayer, Emma, 1906-1919 (Box 106, Folder 1060)
  - Accession 90:076, 1912-1983, bulk 1964-1979; 1964-1979; 11; 15.8 Cubic Feet 36 boxes
    The following subseries are included in Series 11:
    Subseries 1: Administration
    Subseries 2: Graduate Study Fellowships
    Subseries 3: Marsh Island
    Subseries 4: Personnel
    Subseries 5: Programs
    Series 11 of the Russell Sage Foundation Records was added to the collection in 1990 (accession 90-76). It comprises administrative, personnel, and program records similar to those found in Series 2 through 7. The earliest documents in this series, concerning Marsh Island, date from 1912. The remaining records cover the period from 1946 to 1983 with the bulk covering 1964-1979.
    - Administration, 1946-1983; 1; 4.4 Cubic Feet
      The Administration subseries includes agenda for Board of Trustees meetings, budget and financial reports, administrative memoranda, and reports and memoranda evaluating the design and success of various programs and projects.
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees (WEM), February 7, 1968 (Box 107, Folder 1061)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees (Mary), May 7, 1968 (Box 107, Folder 1062)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees (WEM), November 7, 1968 (Box 107, Folder 1063)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees, February 6, 1969 (Box 107, Folder 1064)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees (LC), May 13, 1969 (Box 108, Folder 1065)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees (Mary), November 13, 1969 (Box 108, Folder 1066)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees, February 5, 1970 (Box 108, Folder 1067)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees (OGB), May 5, 1970 (Box 108, Folder 1068)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees (HEF), November 23, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 1069)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees, February 5, 1971 (Box 109, Folder 1070)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees, May 11, 1971 (Box 109, Folder 1071)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees (OGB), November 11, 1971 (Box 109, Folder 1072)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees (OGB), February 10, 1972 (Box 109, Folder 1073)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees, May 11, 1972 (Box 110, Folder 1074)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees (Gus), November 20, 1972 (Box 110, Folder 1075)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees (TC), February 9, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 1076)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees, May 8, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 1077)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees, December 10, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 1078)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees, March 15, 1974 (Box 110, Folder 1079)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees, June 10, 1974 (Box 110, Folder 1080)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees - Proposals to Agenda, June 10, 1974 (Box 110, Folder 1081)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees, December 9, 1974 (Box 111, Folder 1082)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees - Proposals to Agenda, December 9, 1974 (Box 111, Folder 1083)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees, March 13, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 1084)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees - Proposals to Agenda, March 13, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 1085)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees (File), June 9, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 1086)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees - Proposals to Agenda (File), June 9, 1975 (Box 112, Folder 1087)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees - Special Meeting, September 9, 1975 (Box 112, Folder 1088)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees (TC), December 8, 1975 (Box 112, Folder 1089)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees - Proposals to Agenda, December 8, 1975 (Box 112, Folder 1090)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees, January 10, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 1091)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees (DT), March 18-20, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 1092)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees (DT), June 7, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 1093)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees (DT), September 10, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 1094)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees, January 10, 1977 (Box 113, Folder 1095)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees, March 17, 1978 (Box 113, Folder 1096)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees, June 23-25, 1977 (Box 113, Folder 1097)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees (DT), November 20, 1977 (Box 114, Folder 1098)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees, January 20, 1978 (Box 114, Folder 1099)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees, March 17, 1978 (Box 114, Folder 1100)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees - Proposals, May 1978 (Box 114, Folder 1101)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees, June 22-24, 1978 (Box 114, Folder 1102)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees - Proposals to Agenda, June 22-24, 1978 (Box 115, Folder 1103)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees - Proposals to Agenda, June 22-24, 1978 (Box 115, Folder 1104)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees, March 2, 1979 (Box 115, Folder 1105)
      - Agenda, Board of Trustees, June 28-30, 1979 (Box 115, Folder 1106)
      - Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 1107)
      - Finance/Budget Committee - Report, June 7, 1976 (Box 116, Folder 1108)
      - Memoranda - Cline to Staff, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 1109)
      - Memoranda - Staff Memos, 1977 (Box 116, Folder 1110)
      - Memoranda - Staff and Salary, 1946-1952, 1956-1976, undated (Box 116, Folder 1111)
        Restricted - Confidential material.
      - Memoranda - Wildavsky to Board, January 10, 1977 (Box 116, Folder 1112)
      - Minutes, Board of Trustees, June 24, 1977 (Box 116, Folder 1113)
      - Program/Project Design - Bond, Betsy - A Reference to Russell Sage Foundation Program and Related Projects, 1979 (Box 116, Folder 1114)
      - Program/Project Design - Brim, Orville - Memoranda on Russell Sage Foundation, 1964-1970 (Box 116, Folder 1115)
      - Program/Project Design - Douglas, Mary - Program on Culture, 1977-1979 (Box 116, Folder 1116)
      - Program/Project Design - Memoranda, Miscellaneous, 1974-1975, 1978-1979, undated (Box 116, Folder 1117)
      - Program/Project Design - Memoranda, Staff to Staff, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 1118)
      - Program/Project Design - 1972 Evaluation (Box 116, Folder 1119)
      - Program/Project Design - Notes on Socio-legal Research (Wheeler to Wildavsky), 1977 (Box 117, Folder 1120)
      - Program/Project Design - Program Statements, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 1121)
      - Program/Project Design - Radical Consultants, Correspondence, 1971-1973, 1982 (Box 117, Folder 1122)
      - Program/Project Design - "Report on Russell Sage Foundation" by Schulman, Brown, Kahn, 1971 (Box 117, Folder 1123)
      - Program/Project Design - "Report on Russell Sage Foundation" by Schulman, Brown, Kahn, 1971 (Box 117, Folder 1124)
      - Program/Project Design - Self-Evaluations, 1981-1982 (Box 117, Folder 1125)
      - Program/Project Design - Shafer, Byron - Issues in Proposal Review, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 1126)
      - Program/Project Design - Truman, Dave - Project Selection and Monitoring, 1978-1979 (Box 117, Folder 1127)
      - Program/Project Design - Wheeler, Stanton - Conference on Law and the Legal Profession, 1977-1978 (Box 117, Folder 1128)
      - Publications - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 1128a)
      - Treasurer - Report (DT), September 10, 1976 (Box 117, Folder 1129)
    - Graduate Study Fellowships, 1969-1978; 2; 0.4 Cubic Feet
      The Graduate Study Fellowships subseries consists of evaluations of the fellowship program solicited from former fellows, as well as proposals for changes in the program's policies, procedures and emphasis.
      - Continuation of After 1975-76 - Material for AS re Proposal, 1969-1972, 1975, undated (Box 118, Folder 1130)
      - Curricula Vitae, 1974-1975, undated (Box 118, Folder 1131)
      - Evaluations, 1975 (Box 118, Folder 1132)
      - Letters of Recommendation, 1975-1976, 1978 (Box 118, Folder 1133)
      - Memoranda, 1969, 1972, 1975-1976 (Box 118, Folder 1134)
      - Sub-file - Barron, Paula, 1975-1978, undated (Box 118, Folder 1135)
      - Sub-file - Cherlin, Andrew, 1975-1976 (Box 118, Folder 1136)
      - Sub-file - Dawkins, Marvin, 1974-1975 (Box 118, Folder 1137)
      - Sub-file - Grandjean, Burke, 1975-1976 (Box 118, Folder 1138)
      - Sub-file - Seron, Carroll, 1975, undated (Box 118, Folder 1139)
      - Sub-file - Shafer, Byron, 1974-1975, undated (Box 118, Folder 1140)
    - Marsh Island, 1912-1979; 3; 2.2 Cubic Feet
      This subseries is arranged chronologically.
      The Marsh Island subseries includes legal and administrative material on the ownership and control of Marsh Island, the condition of its bird refuge, and oil-drilling leases.
      - Marsh Island, 1912, 1916, 1920-1921, 1923, 1927, 1931-1939 (Box 118, Folder 1141)
      - Marsh Island, 1940-1941 (Box 118, Folder 1142)
      - Marsh Island, 1942-1944 (Box 119, Folder 1143)
      - Marsh Island, 1945-1948 (Box 119, Folder 1144)
      - Marsh Island, 1949-1956 (Box 119, Folder 1145)
      - Marsh Island, 1957 (Box 119, Folder 1146)
      - Marsh Island, 1958-1959 (Box 119, Folder 1147)
      - Marsh Island, 1960-1962 (Box 120, Folder 1148)
      - Marsh Island, 1963 (Box 120, Folder 1149)
      - Marsh Island, 1963 (Box 120, Folder 1150)
      - Marsh Island, 1964 (Box 120, Folder 1151)
      - Marsh Island, 1964 (Box 120, Folder 1152)
      - Marsh Island, 1965 (Box 120, Folder 1153)
      - Marsh Island, 1966 (Box 121, Folder 1154)
      - Marsh Island, 1966 (Box 121, Folder 1155)
      - Marsh Island, 1967 (Box 121, Folder 1156)
      - Marsh Island, 1967 (Box 121, Folder 1157)
      - Marsh Island, 1967 (Box 121, Folder 1158)
      - Marsh Island, 1968 (Box 121, Folder 1159)
      - Marsh Island, 1968 (Box 122, Folder 1160)
      - 1968 Review (Box 122, Folder 1161)
      - Marsh Island, 1969 (Box 122, Folder 1162)
      - Marsh Island, 1969 (Box 122, Folder 1163)
      - 1969 Current Review (Box 122, Folder 1164)
      - 1969 Current Review (Box 122, Folder 1165)
      - 1970 Current Review (Box 123, Folder 1166)
      - Marsh Island, 1970-1972 (Box 123, Folder 1167)
      - Marsh Island, 1974-1975 (Box 123, Folder 1168)
      - Marsh Island, 1976-1977, 1979 (Box 123, Folder 1169)
      - Division Orders, Stipulations of Interest, Etc., 1954, 1960-1965, 1967-1971 (Box 123, Folder 1170)
      - Division Orders, Stipulations of Interest, Etc., 1954, 1960-1965, 1967-1971 (Box 123, Folder 1171)
      - Division Orders, Stipulations of Interest, Etc., 1954, 1960-1965, 1967-1971 (Box 123, Folder 1172)
      - Finances, 1957, 1961-1963 (Box 124, Folder 1173)
      - Project Estimates and Costs, 1955-1957 (Box 124, Folder 1174)
      - Reports - Progress and Financial, 1958-1970, undated (Box 124, Folder 1175)
      - Reports - Progress and Financial, 1958-1970, undated (Box 124, Folder 1176)
      - Reports - Progress and Financial, 1958-1970, undated (Box 124, Folder 1177)
      - Theall Suit, 1969 (Box 124, Folder 1178)
    - Personnel, 1965-1979; 4; 1 Cubic Feet
      The Personnel subseries documents the work of various Russell Sage Foundation employees, primarily staff members, fellows and visiting scholars, while at the Foundation and subsequently. Throughout these files are scattererd hand-written notes by the same person. The author of these notes is not identified but appears to be Arthur Shore, who joined the Russell Sage Foundation staff in 1972 and served as Executive Manager (1976) and Vice President (1976-1979).
      - Consultants - Andrews, F. Emerson, 1967, 1971, undated (Box 124, Folder 1179)
      - Fellows - Grandjean, Burke, 1978 (Box 124, Folder 1180)
      - Fellows - Guttenberg, Richard, 1978 (Box 124, Folder 1181)
      - Fellows - Spitz, Elaine, 1977-1979 (Box 124, Folder 1182)
      - Others/Unidentified - Goslink, David/NAS, 1976-1978 (Box 124, Folder 1183)
      - Others/Unidentified - Graymer, Leroy, 1976-1977 (Box 124, Folder 1184)
      - Others/Unidentified - Hess, Beth, 1975-1976 (Box 125, Folder 1185)
      - Others/Unidentified - Marshall, Shelley, 1975-1976 (Box 125, Folder 1186)
      - Others/Unidentified - Marshall, Shelley, 1976 (Box 125, Folder 1186a)
      - Others/Unidentified - Morss, Elliott (Commission on Federal Paperwork), 1976 (Box 125, Folder 1187)
      - Others/Unidentified - Sherman, Malcolm J., 1977 (Box 125, Folder 1188)
      - Others/Unidentified - Truman, David, 1978-1979 (Box 125, Folder 1189)
      - Others/Unidentified - Truman, David, 1978-1979 (Box 125, Folder 1190)
      - Staff - Applegath, John, 1978, undated (Box 125, Folder 1191)
      - Staff - Freeman, Howard E., 1976-1977, undated (Box 125, Folder 1192)
      - Staff - Nexon, David, 1976-1977 (Box 125, Folder 1193)
      - Staff - Nexon, David, 1976-1977 (Box 125, Folder 1194)
      - Staff - Riley, Matilda White, 1976-1977 (Box 125, Folder 1195)
      - Staff - Terranova, Diane, 1975-1978 (Box 125, Folder 1196)
      - Staff - Wallace, Walter M., 1976-1977 (Box 125, Folder 1197)
      - Staff - Waring, Joan, 1975-1977 (Box 125, Folder 1198)
      - Staff - Weil, Joyce, 1969-1971 (Box 125, Folder 1199)
      - Staff - Yoder, Jean, 1975-1977, undated (Box 125, Folder 1200)
      - Staff - Yoder, Jean, 1975-1977, undated (Box 125, Folder 1201)
      - Visiting Scholars - General, 1965-1975 (Box 125, Folder 1202)
      - Visiting Scholars - Glass, David C., 1969-1976 (Box 126, Folder 1203)
      - Visiting Scholars - Glazer, Nathan, 1977-1978 (Box 126, Folder 1204)
      - Visiting Scholars - Grossman, David, 1976 (Box 126, Folder 1205)
      - Visiting Scholars - Grossman, David, 1976-1977 (Box 126, Folder 1206)
      - Visiting Scholars - Grossman, David, 1976-1977 (Box 126, Folder 1207)
      - Visiting Scholars - Inbar, Michael, 1976 (Box 126, Folder 1208)
      - Visiting Scholars - Katz, Stanley, 1976, 1978-1979 (Box 126, Folder 1209)
      - Visiting Scholars - Majone, Giandomenico, 1977, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 1210)
      - Visiting Scholars - van Gunsteren, Herman, 1977 (Box 126, Folder 1211)
    - Programs, 1955-1979; 5; 6.4 Cubic Feet
      This subseries is arranged alphabetically by investigator within each of the following program areas: Age and Aging Citizenship; Civil Liberties and Social Control; Developing the Social Sciences; Evaluation Research and Organizational Performance; Government; Historical Studies of Social Policy; Law/Law and the Social Sciences; Mass Media and the Social Sciences; Philanthropy; Policy Analysis; Race, Ethnicity, and Gender; Social Change; Social Sciences and Human Biology; and Technical Policy Studies.
      The Programs subseries focuses on the administration of Russell Sage Foundation-funded projects as well as the design, implementation and results of the projects. The project files, uneven in their content, may include proposals, administrative correspondence, status and final reports, supporting documents such as reprints and conference material, and information on related, non-Russell Sage Foundation projects.
      - Age and Aging - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 126, Folder 1212)
      - Age and Aging - Mailing List, 1975 (Box 126, Folder 1213)
      - Age and Aging - Mailing List, 1976 (Box 127, Folder 1214)
      - Age and Aging - Reports on Program, 1974-1975 (Box 127, Folder 1215)
      - Age and Aging - Status of Projects, 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 1216)
      - Age and Aging - Baltes, Paul - Cognitive Development and Modifiability in Adulthood, 1975-1976 (Box 127, Folder 1217)
      - Age and Aging - Boocock, Sarane - Continuation of Research on the Status of Children and the Child Care System, 1973-1978 (Box 127, Folder 1218)
      - Age and Aging - Bronfenbrenner, Urie and Goslin, David - Education and Child Rearing in China, 1972-1976 (Box 127, Folder 1219)
      - Age and Aging - Kertzer, David and Foner, Anne - Dynamics of Age Stratification: The Latuka in Transition, 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 1220)
      - Age and Aging - Marini, Margaret Mooney - Transition from Adolescence to Adulthood, 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 1221)
      - Age and Aging - Marini, Margaret Mooney - Transition from Adolescence to Adulthood, 1974-1977 (Box 128, Folder 1222)
      - Age and Aging - Marini, Margaret Mooney - Transition from Adolescence to Adulthood, 1974-1975 (Box 128, Folder 1222a)
      - Age and Aging - Presser, Harriet - Age at Motherhood: Social Consequences, 1975-1976 (Box 128, Folder 1223)
      - Age and Aging - Riley, Matilda White - Project on the Aging and Society, 1973-1980 (Box 128, Folder 1224)
      - Age and Aging - Riley, Matilda White - Project on the Aging and Society, 1973-1980 (Box 128, Folder 1225)
      - Age and Aging - Scott, Anne - Analysis of the Biographical Material on the Graduates of the Troy Female Seminary, 1976-1977 (Box 128, Folder 1226)
      - Age and Aging - Smelser, Neil - Institutional Change, Changes in Age Structure, and the Life Course, 1975-1977 (Box 128, Folder 1227)
      - Age and Aging - Zablocki, Benjamin - Comparative Study of Day Care in Six Large American Cities, 1975-1979 (Box 128, Folder 1228)
      - Citizenship - Workshop, 1977-1978 (Box 128, Folder 1229)
      - Citizenship - McClosky, Herbert - General Correspondence, 1978 (Box 128, Folder 1230)
      - Citizenship - Proposals - Master List, 1978 (Box 128, Folder 1231)
      - Civil Liberties and Social Control - Nexon, David - The Police, the Public and Civil Liberties (Pilot Phase), 1976-1977 (Box 129, Folder 1232)
      - Developing the Social Sciences - Becker, Howard - Potential Use of Documentary Photography in Social Science Research, 1972-1977 (Box 129, Folder 1233)